propelmedia.com 2015-11-27

# Propel Media - Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains what information Propel Media, Inc. (“Propel Media”, also referred to as “we”, “us”, or “our”) collects from individuals who visit the PropelMedia.com website (the “Site”). The Privacy Policy also explains how Propel Media uses and maintains that information.

Changes to the Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to update or modify the Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on the Site under the tab “Privacy Policy” or other places on the Site that we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Any changes to the Privacy Policy will be effective as of the date indicated at the bottom of the Privacy Policy, so please review it frequently.

This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected on the Site and not to information collected or obtained from other sources.

Information Collected

We collect two kinds of information through the Site. The first kind of information is Personally Identifiable Information that can identify you as a specific individual, such as your name and email address (“PII”). We only collect PII when you have contacted us directly (see “Collection of Personally Identifiable Information” below). The second kind of information is the kind of non-personally identifiable information (“NPII”) collected and stored automatically by many websites. It includes, for example, information about your Internet service provider, operating system, type of browser, geographic location, and pages viewed on the Site. Although this information is related to you, it is not associated with your PII and cannot be linked to you personally.

If you do not want your information to be collected and used as provided in this Privacy Policy, you should not access or use the Site.

Collection of Personally Identifiable Information

PII is collected by the Site only when you provide it to us via the “Contact” page or the contact section on the bottom of PropelMedia.com, in which the Site asks for your name and email address so that you can receive a response to any questions you may have.

If you do not want us to collect your PII as described above or to use and share your PII as described further below in this Privacy Policy, you should NOT provide it to us through any of the Site features described above. By providing us with your PII through use of these features, you are authorizing our use and sharing of your PII as described in this Privacy Policy and any subsequent revisions to this Privacy Policy that we may publish on the Site.

Social Media Features and Widgets

The Site includes Social Media Features and Widgets (“Features and Widgets”), such as Propel Media profiles on Facebook, Twitter and Linkedin, or other interactive mini-programs that run on our Site. These Features and Widgets may collect your PII via a login, IP address, and may set a cookie to enable these functions properly. Features and Widgets are hosted by a third party and therefore, your interactions with these Features and Widgets are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

Updating Your Personally Identifiable Information

We will retain your information for as long as needed to provide you services, or as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolution of disputes, and enforcement of our agreements. You may update, correct, amend or request to remove your PII from our systems by emailing us at [info@PropelMedia.com](mailto:info@propelmedia.com) or by calling us at (866) 394-1786.

Children’s Privacy

The Site and all information, content and materials contained on the Site (in any form or media, the “Site Materials”) are neither intended for, nor directed to, nor to be accessed by, persons under the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect PII from anyone under 13 years of age. We cannot and will not independently verify that all those who use the Site are at least 13 years old, but we will remove from our files any PII of anyone we discover to be under 13 years old.

Use and Sharing of Personally Identifiable Information

We reserve the right to use PII: (1) for the specific purpose for which such information was provided as stated above; (2) for the purposes disclosed at the time such information is provided; or (3) as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

We do not share, sell or trade any of your PII with any third parties other than described herein. We may share your PII with our principals, officers, directors, members, employees, consultants, agents, subsidiaries or affiliates (collectively, “Related Entities”). Neither we nor our Related Entities contribute to or participate in cooperative databases, which give other companies access to your PII.

We and our Related Entities may provide access to your PII when legally required to do so, to comply with a court order, to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Site, to limit our legal liability and protect our rights or to protect the rights, property or safety of other users or the public.

We and/or our Related Entities may also disclose your PII to outside companies and consultants that help bring you the services we offer. For example, we and our Related Entities may work with outside companies and consultants to: (a) manage a database of client information; (b) assist in distributing emails; (c) assist with direct marketing and data collection; (d) provide data storage and analysis; (e) provide fraud prevention; (f) provide customer service by phone; and/or (g) provide other services designed to assist us in maximizing our business potential and maintaining our Site. We and our Related Entities require that these outside companies and consultants agree to keep confidential all information we share with them, and use the information only to perform their obligations to us.

In addition, if we or our Related Entities go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your PII will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified by a prominent notice on the Site of any such change in ownership or control of your PII.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information

As with many websites, when you visit our Site, it automatically gathers certain NPII based on your computer information and stores it in log files. This type of technical and statistical information is used to customize your experience on the Site, to help us improve the quality of the Site and to make your visits to the Site easy and convenient. The Site also collects your IP address to help diagnose problems with the Site server and for Site administration purposes.

Cookies

A “cookie” is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.

We use cookies to collect aggregate Internet traffic statistics and to better understand our users, which allow us to enhance your experience at the Site. This data may include storing user preferences and product utilization information such as number of visitors, average time spent on pages, features used, and other information which help us determine which features are most important to you and working effectively.

If you do not want the Site to deploy cookies in your browser, you can set your browser to reject cookies or to notify you when a website tries to put a cookie in your browser software. If you choose to decline cookies, however, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Site and it may affect your ability to use some of the services at the Site. We do not tie any PII to the cookies that we set.

Web Beacons

The Site may contain electronic images known as “web beacons” which are also sometimes called single-pixel gifs. Web beacons may be used to assist in delivering cookies, allow us to count users who have visited the Site pages.

We may also employ web beacons from third party partners in order to help compile aggregated statistics regarding the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns or other operations of the Site. We will never allow web beacons on the Site to be used by third parties to collect or access your PII. We do not tie web beacons to any PII you submit while on our Site.

Use and Sharing of Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We share NPII with our business partners in order to customize the services they and we provide to you. And of course, we may also disclose any of the NPII collected through the Site in order to: (1) comply with applicable laws, (2) respond to governmental inquiries, (3) comply with valid legal process, or (4) protect our rights and property or that of or our users.

We reserve the right to use NPII: (1) for the specific purpose for which such information was provided as stated above; (2) for the purposes disclosed at the time such information is provided; or (3) as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

We do not share, sell or trade any of your NPII with any third parties other than described herein. We may share your NPII with our Related Entities. Neither we nor our Related Entities contribute to or participate in cooperative databases, which give other Entities access to your PII.

We and our Related Entities may provide access to your NPII when legally required to do so, to comply with a court order, to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Site, to limit our legal liability and protect our rights or to protect the rights, property or safety of other users or the public.

We and/or our Related Entities may also disclose your NPII to outside companies and consultants that help bring you the services we offer. For example, we and our Related Entities may work with outside companies and consultants to: (a) manage a database of client information; (b) assist in distributing emails; (c) assist with direct marketing and data collection; (d) provide data storage and analysis; (e) provide fraud prevention; (f) provide customer service by phone; and/or (g) provide other services designed to assist us in maximizing our business potential and maintaining our Site. We and our Related Entities require that these outside companies and consultants agree to keep confidential all information we share with them, and use the information only to perform their obligations to us.

In addition, if we or our Related Entities go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your NPII will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified by a prominent notice on the Site of any such change in ownership or control of your NPII.

Security

We have implemented technical, administrative and physical security measures to protect Information from unauthorized access and improper use. We keep information on servers that are protected by firewalls and located in a physically secure facility accessible only to authorized employees. From time to time, we review our security procedures in order to consider appropriate new technology and methods. Please be aware though, that, despite our reasonable efforts, no security measures are impenetrable and any connection to the Site or information transmitted to us or to the Site will be at your own risk.

Links from the Site

The Site may provide links to the websites of our business partners. If you link to any of these third party web sites, this Privacy Policy will not apply to your use of, and activities on, those sites. We encourage you to read the legal notices posted on these web sites, including their privacy policies. We shall have no responsibility or liability for your visitation to, and the data collection and use practices of, these sites. All inquiries concerning the use of PII by a third party must be communicated to that third party and not to us.

Your California Privacy Rights

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal customer information we share with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates’ direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request by email to [legal@PropelMedia.com](mailto:legal@propelmedia.com). Please allow 30 days for a response.

QUESTIONS AND CONCERNS

If you have any questions or concerns about the Privacy Policy or its implementation, please email us at [legal@PropelMedia.com](mailto:legal@propelmedia.com). For general questions about the Site, please email us at [info@PropelMedia.com](mailto:info@propelmedia.com). Alternatively, you may call us at (866) 394-1786 or write to us at Propel Media, Inc., 2010 Main Street, Suite 900, Irvine, CA 92614, Attn: Legal Department.

Effective: March 3, 2015
